policeauctions.com 2008-12-16

# Privacy Policy

**Police Auctions.com Privacy Statement**

**Here are important FAQs on PoliceAuctions.com and the information the site collects**.

PoliceAuctions.com, published by privately held Vortal Group, Inc., is an online directory of government and non-government auctions. The information we gather cannot be used by the public, including visitors, other members, or anyone not employed by Vortal Group, Inc. or the financial institutions used to process membership charges, to identify specific individuals. 

We collect credit card, address, or bank information only from those who choose to join the service at the paid subscription level. 

**What type of information does PoliceAuctions.com Collect?**

There are two types of information that PoliceAuctions.com collects. One, information users submit to us and two, information not directly submitted by users.

**User Information submitted to PoliceAuctions.com**

The user information submitted to PoliceAuctions.com is separated into two categories: Public and Private. The Public information is the personal information that may be displayed on the site at the discretion of the user, such as username or email address in connection with a voluntary posting by the user on a message board, chat or other public posting through the system. The Private information is the user's email address and credit card information. 

**User Information that's Private:**

Private information is the user's email address, and credit card or other payment information which could include first name, last name, credit card number or checking account information for payment, a user-specified password, mailing address, zip code and telephone number.

**Surveys**

All participation in our surveys is voluntary and is anonymous.

**Affiliate Partners for PoliceAuctions.com**

PoliceAuctions.com's Affiliate program allows other sites to link to the PoliceAuctions.com site. No personal member information is exchanged with the Affiliate Partner, with the following exception: Sites that incentivize their members to join PoliceAuctions.com require those users' email addresses for verification. PoliceAuctions.com sends the users' email address back to the referring site so they can track their incentives. PoliceAuctions.com may create mirror versions of its site that draw from the same database. Those sites will display user's public information under the same conditions as the primary PoliceAuctions.com site. 

**User Information not Directly Submitted to PoliceAuctions.com**

**PoliceAuctions.com** collects information that is not personally identifiable, such as browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all users to the site.

**How is Information obtained by PoliceAuctions.com used?:**

**User information that's Public:** Public information supplied by the user may at the user's discretion be viewed by visitors to the site. Visitors use this information for correspondence purposes. A user's public information cannot be used to identify a specific member by name, address, or other criteria.  
**  
User information that's Private:** User's email addresses submitted by members are primarily used to verify registration. Users' email addresses are not disclosed to other members unless the user gives permission to do so through his user settings. Vortal Group, Inc.also uses a user's email address to send news and updates of functionality of PoliceAuctions.com. Vortal Group, Inc. also uses a user's email address to send them content and offers from other sites that Vortal Group, Inc. publishes. The user may choose not to receive email of this type by using the opt-out link included in any such email.

Vortal Group, Inc. may also use user's email addresses for private correspondence with the user for customer service issues. User Financial information collected by PoliceAuctions.com is used to bill the user for products and services. Any other private information submitted by the user is confidential and will not be disclosed except as required by law. All of user's private information can be updated or deleted by the user at any time.

**Does PoliceAuctions.com share your information?**

**Vortal Group, Inc. does not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your private information to any outside parties, except to the financial institution that processes your credit card or check transaction unless required by law or for the protection of your membership. It is the policy of PoliceAuctions.com to cooperate with all law enforcement investigations, which includes disclosing all user info, both public and private, to any law enforcement agency.**

**What about links?**

PoliceAuctions.com may link to other websites. PoliceAuctions.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other Web sites.

**Does PoliceAuctions.com use Cookies?**

PoliceAuctions.com uses cookies to manage access to the different areas of the website. Should the user disable cookies on their browser, they will have difficulty navigating the site and using its features. PoliceAuctions.com does not use cookies for collection of private information.

**How do you correct, modify, or update information?**

For modifying or removing user information from our database, PoliceAuctions.com gives users the following options:

1\. Users can modify information by logging into the members page with their user id and password.

2\. Users can send email to [support@PoliceAuctions.com](mailto:support@policeauctions.com)

3\. Users can send mail to the following postal address:10061 Talbert Ave. #204, Fountain Valley, CA 92708

**What about changes in PoliceAuctions.com's Privacy Policy?**

From time to time, our privacy policy may require amendments. If the change is significant, we will prominently post a link to those changes on our homepage. Users will always have a choice to cancel their membership and end their participation in the site when changes to the privacy policy are made.  
**  
How do I contact PoliceAuctions.com?**

For any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us directly:

1\. By e-mail [support@PoliceAuctions.com](mailto:support@policeauctions.com)

2\. By Phone 1-714-963-4900

3\. By snail mail: 10061 Talbert Ave., #204, Fountain Valley, CA 92708
